driversupdated.com 2014-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Orient International Group

**Privacy Policy**

Orient International Group ("OIG", "we" or "us"), has developed this Privacy Policy to explain all our reasonable precautions to keep any personal data ("Data") secure. This website may include hyperlinks to third-party websites, which are completely beyond the control of OIG. This Privacy Policy only applies to this website and OIG is not responsible for the content of the privacy practices of third-party websites. This Privacy Policy may be updated without notice. We therefore invite you to return to this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to familiarize yourself with any changes.

**Processing of Data by OIG**

OIG does not collect personally identifying Data from this website except when specifically and knowingly provided by you. We do log your internet protocol ("IP") address for purposes of administrating or compiling demographic information and of monitoring usage and performance of this website. We do make use of tracking technology ("Cookies") to gather such data as browser type and operating system, metrics, geographical location and understanding how visitors use this website.

**Data Security**

We undertake to take all reasonable steps in order not to allow your Data to be seen by any third parties. We will only disclose your Data to other third parties, if required to do so for legal or regulatory purposes.

**Acceptance**

By visiting this website, communicating with us and submitting your personal data to this website, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way and to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Governing Law**

This Privacy Policy is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the United Kingdom. You agree to submit any dispute arising out of your use of this website to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of The United Kingdom.
